http://www.aceproject.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy Statement
This privacy statement covers the site [www.aceproject.com]. Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to its users' privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices.
If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should first contact Daniel Raymond by email at support@aceproject.com.
Also, a specific section has been added to this page for privacy policy information to align with the GDPR requirements. You can go directly to GDPR info section.
Information Collection and Use
Information Collection
[Websystems Inc.] is the sole owner of the information collected on [www.aceproject.com]. [Websystems Inc.] collects information from its users at several different points on our Web site.
Registration
In order to use this Web site, a user must first create a free account. During registration a user is required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to send requested email notifications, to contact our customers for major announcements or to fix account-related issues, such as payment issues.
Order
Our authorized payment processor requests information from the user for billing purpose only. The user must provide contact information (such as name, email, and billing address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). If our authorized payment processor has trouble processing an order, the information is used by our support team to contact the user.
Information Use
Profile
We store information that we collect through cookies and dynamic asp pages to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that detail their viewing preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the users' personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user's visit to our Web site. We do not share users profiles with other third parties.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use cookies to remember your Account ID, username and password. We do not share your cookie with other third parties.
Dynamic ASP Pages
We use dynamic ASP forms to collect information like company information, projects, timesheets, users, tasks, files attachments, notes, and preferences. We do not share your information with other third parties.
Log Files
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movements in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. Website visitor IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. On the other hand, IP addresses of the AceProject application users are linked to personally identifiable information for security considerations, management of connections, support and improvement of overall user experience.
We use a tracking utility called Google Analytics that uses log files to analyze user movement.
Password Encryption
Passwords are encrypted with the "md5" crytographic algorhitm. Thus, passwords are case sensitive and are visible neither by us nor by your account's administrators. This puts the level of security of your data at a very high level. If your forgot your password, you will have to use the "Forgot Password?" link to enter a new one, since it cannot be retreived.
Communication from the Site
We do not share users' emails with other third parties, we do not spam, and we do not offer an ad-supported software as a service.
Special Offers and Updates
We send all new members a welcoming email to verify email, username, and password. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users, we present the option not to receive these types of communications.
Newsletter
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications.
Service Announcements
On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service-related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send users an email or put an alert on the login page. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.
Customer Service
We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the users wishes.
Email Notification
Each user may decide to receive an email when he or she is assigned to a new task, or when one of his or her tasks is modified. This frees the project manager's time for more important tasks - email notification is automatic.
Sharing
Legal Disclaimer
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.
These are the instances in which we will share users' personal information:
Business Transitions
In the event that [Websystems Inc.] goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Users will be notified via email, a prominent notice would be placed on our Web site for 30 days, prior to a change of ownership or control of their personal information. If, as a result of the business transition, the users' personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, they will be given choice consistent with our notification of changes section.
Choice/Opt-out
Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying with "unsubscribe" in the subject line in the email or email us at support@aceproject.com.
Links
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, [Websystems Inc.], are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
Security
This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the application, their information is protected both online and off-line.
Furthermore, your payment information is encrypted and protected before even leaving your computer via the best encryption technology in the industry - SSL.
Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users' personally identifiable information. This can usually be done from the "Account information page" or by emailing our Customer Service at support@aceproject.com.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we can use their information in this different manner. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.
Privacy information (GDPR - updated May 2018)
Your Personal Data:
What we need
We only collect basic personal data about you and includes one special type of information or location based information, specifically, your IP address. The basic personal information includes name, address, email when subscribing to our services, etc.
Why we need it
We need to know your basic personal data in order to provide you with notice writing and analysis services in line with this overall contract. We will not collect any personal data from you we do not need in order to provide and oversee this service to you. The IP address is stored in access logs to help in technical support cases.
What we do with it
All the personal data we process is processed by our staff in Canada however for the purposes of IT hosting and maintenance this information is located on servers within the United States. No 3rd parties have access to your personal data unless the law allows them to do so. A 3rd party payment system, called Chargebee/Stripe, is used for credit card processing. Card details and name of account holder and address is stored by them.We have a Data Protection regime in place to oversee the effective and secure processing of your personal data.
How long we keep it
We keep your basic personal data (name, address, contact details) for a reasonable minimum time before it will be destroyed (usually 90 days after a cancelled/closed account). Your information we use for marketing purposes will be kept with us until you notify us that you no longer wish to receive this information. History billing information is kept for accounting and tax purposes.
What we would also like to do with it
We would however like to use your name and email address to inform you of our future offers and similar products. This information is not shared with third purposes and you can unsubscribe at any time via email.
What are your rights?
If at any point you believe the information we process on you is incorrect you can request to see this information and even have it corrected or deleted in a reasonable timeframe. If you wish to raise a complaint on how we have handled your personal data, you can contact our Support Team who will investigate the matter.
If you are not satisfied with our response or believe we are processing your personal data not in accordance with the law you can complain to the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO).
For any questions, you can contact us at support@aceproject.com
